blackink2.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy for Quit Your Day Job

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site as well as our products and services.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

**1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

**Registration Information:**

You will provide us information about yourself when you register to become a member of Quit Your Day Job, register for certain services, or register for email newsletters and alerts.

When you sign-up for our newsletter we collect your name and e-mail address. This is used for our own internal purposes and is not shared with any third party.

**Agents**

We use an outside billing company (ClickBank - [www.clickbank.com](http://www.clickbank.com/)) to process credit card orders and bill you for goods and services purchased through our website. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

**Service Providers**

We use Aweber ([www.aweber.com](http://www.aweber.com/)) to handle all of our e-mail auto-responders and newsletter sign-ups. When you sign-up for our newsletter, we share your e-mail and name with Aweber as necessary for Aweber to provide this service. This information is not used for any other purpose. 

**Email Information:**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. 

**Bulletin Boards/Forums:**

Once you have purchased one of our products or services you may have access to our exclusive members-only forums. If you decide to use the forums on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

Any member of the forum who sends unsolicited messages to other members may be permanently removed from our forums. If you have received an unsolicited message from any member of the forum, please let us know by e-mailing us at <http://www.quityourdayjob.com/contact>. 

**2\. Web Site Usage Information:**

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small pieces of code called “clear gifs” to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.

Some of our business partners; including advertisers, and web analytics providers use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by [www.quityourdayjob.com](http://www.quityourdayjob.com/ "www.quityourdayjob.com") only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at <http://www.quityourdayjob.com/contact>

**What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

As you shop on our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other shoppers so your shopping cart is only available to you. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We will not sell or share your personally identifiable information with any third party. 

**Notice of New Services and Changes**

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request at <http://www.quityourdayjob.com/contact>

### Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by e-mailing us at [unsubscribe@quityourdayjob.com](mailto:unsubscribe@quityourdayjob.com).

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. 

### **How Do We Protect Your Information?**

**Security**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can e-mail us at <http://www.quityourdayjob.com/contact>. 

**How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?**

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. 

**How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing <http://www.quityourdayjob.com/contact>. You can also change any of your subscription options by following the directions in any of our newsletters. 

**Certain Disclosures**

 ****We may disclosure your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or Affiliated Parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, the Site, the users of the Site, and/or our Affiliated Parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of the Site, us, or third parties.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

**Quit Your Day Job, LLC Contact Information**

Quit Your Day Job

10011 S. Centennial Pkwy

Ste 320

Sandy, UT 84070

<http://www.quityourdayjob.com/contact>

**Model Disclosure**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by e-mail, or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

**Privacy Policy Effective Date**

May 4, 2006

**Last Updated**

April 3, 2008
